LUSTIYANA

Phone 082217647776 LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/lustiyana-lustiyana-59959b20b

E-mail lustiyana1801@gmail.com **GitHub** https://github.com/Lustiyana

Personal Profile

I'm a final year student of Informatics. Some abilities in Web Programming like HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, and PHP and some framework like Bootstrap, Tailwindcss and React JS (Next JS). I have target to graduate in 2023. I also have the ability to operate Microsoft Office like Ms. Word, Ms. Excel, Power Point, and Ms. Access (Including Google Sheets and Google Docs) I have skills in public speaking and able to work with team. I have critical thinking and some experience in terms of brainstorming.

Educational

2019 - Present Informatics Engineering

Islamic State University Sunan Gunung Djati GPA 3.8

Working Experience

2022-11 - 2022-04 Internship

Direktorat Jenderal Pendidikan Islam Kementrian Agama Republik Indonesia

- Create design for Web Profile
- Implementing Design into the Web
- Testing the Web

2022-07 - 2022-09 Quality Assurance Intern

Greeneration Foundation

- Assist the Quality Assurance process for the Website Project landing page process Driving Refill Solutions 2.0
- Ensure and carry out the process of monitoring the quality of the Project Driving Website Refill Solutions 2.0
- Assist the IT team in the process of brainstorming and internal discussions
- Create Testcase document for Greeneration Foundation Web, Driving Refill Solutions Web, and GFDP Web
- Checking web Greeneration Foundation Web, Driving Refill Solutions Web, and GFDP Web

2021-08 – 2021-12 Private Tutor of Computer and Preschool Education

Eduprima Group

Teach excel program for Highschool student

- Excel base and function in excel
- Pivot table
- Introduction to micro services

Teach reading, writing, and arithmetic for preschool student

- Designing learning media for pre-school children

Skills and Interest

Have some basic web development (HTML, CSS)

Can use bootstrap and tailwindcss css frameworks

Able in several programming languages including Python, Java, C, C++, PHP, and Javascript

Able in React Js framework (Next Js)

Can use Postman for API testing

Google IT Automation certification from Coursera

DeepLearning.AI Tensorflow Developer from Coursera

Matematics for Machine Learning from Coursera

Structuring Machine Learning Projects from Coursera

Tensorflow: Data and Deployment from Coursera

Machine Learning Graduated from Bangkit Academy 2022

Database Design certification from Oracle Academy

Database Programming with SQL certification from Oracle Academy

Cisco Networking Academy course CCNA: Introduction to Network

Basic Intensive English Program from Language Center in Kampung Inggris

Participants go through the process of validating the E-Wallet User Research Challenge from Indosat

Member and treasurer of Robotics Club UIN Sunan Gunung Djati (2019 – Present)

Member of Program and Partnership of GDSC UIN Sunan Gunung Djati (2021 – Present)